Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Architecture, Yale University, records
1948-2013
RU 1048
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
36
(41 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, course materials, subject files, clippings, faculty records, and minutes of the Rules Committee documenting the Yale School of Architecture and its predecessors.
Yale University. School of Architecture
Harris, Walter
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 19-A (YRG 19-A), Central records and records of the dean of the School of Architecture.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the School of Architecture, 2007-2017; gift of William S. Huff, 2008-2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, course materials, subject files, clippings, faculty records, and minutes of the Rules Committee documenting the Yale School of Architecture and its predecessors.
Architecture -- Study and teaching; Schools of architecture; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Curricula; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University. School of Architecture
- Central records of the School of Architecture, 1956-2006; Accession 2007-A-194
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  - Need/Demand/Supply Exercise, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Housing and LUI SMSA, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Student Work, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Intro to Housing, Deed/Demand Analyses, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Financing Exercise, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Housing Market Analysis, 1980 (Box 1)
  - B.E.S.T, undated (Box 1)
  - Admission Committee Rec Ballot, undated (Box 1)
  - Exams, 1978 (Box 1)
  - M.E.D Student Work, undated (Box 1)
  - M.E.D. Research maria DeAlmeida, undated (Box 1)
  - E99 Spring 73, 1973 (Box 1)
  - E99 Spring 76, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Un Grad, 1973-74 (Box 1)
  - Pre-Major Revision, undated (Box 1)
  - Final Exams, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Prospective M.E.D. Students in City Planning/Urban Development, undated (Box 1)
  - Llano Illustrations, undated (Box 1)
  - Assorted Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - City Planning II, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - Mountain Institute (Kentucky), undated (Box 2)
  - Budget Data, 1965-66 (Box 2)
  - Budget Data, 1964-65 (Box 2)
  - Budget Data, 1963-64 (Box 2)
  - Committees, 1966-67 (Box 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1966-67 (Box 2)
  - Art and Architecture Bldg, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Administration of School of Architecture, 1967-68 (Box 2)
  - Appalachia, 1966-67 (Box 2)
  - Administration I, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - Administration, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - A and A Bldg, undated (Box 2)
  - Black Workshop I, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - Budgets, undated (Box 2)
  - Computer Center, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Deferments, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - Furnishings, undated (Box 2)
  - Gifts and Grants, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Student Summer Committee, undated (Box 2)
  - Governance, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - Graduation, 1970 (Box 2)
  - honorarium, 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - Letters of Recommendation (students), 1969-70 (Box 2)
  - MED, undated (Box 2)
  - NEA, undated (Box 2)
  - President's Office, 1967-68 (Box 2)
  - Provost's Office, 1967-68 (Box 2)
  - Space Requirements, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Yale Arts Association, undated (Box 2)
  - Class Materials
    - Arch 45A-Arch 912, 1963-67 (Box 3)
    - Arch 45A-Arch 145, 1961-67 (Box 4)
    - Subject Files, 1966-79 (Box 5)
    - Housing Seminar Scrapbooks, 1973-78 (Box 6)
    - Course Outlines, 1960s-1980s (Box 6)
  - Departmental Records
    - Correspondence, 1956-87 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence and Review Documentation, 1976-82 (Box 8)
    - Women's Liason Committee, 1976-78 (Box 8)
    - Theses Proposals, 1976-84 (Box 8)
    - Subject Files, 1965-90 (Box 9)
    - Subject Files, 1965-90 (Box 10)
  - Rules Committee
    - 1977-78 (Box 11)
    - 1977 (Box 11)
    - 1976 (Box 11)
    - 1981-82 (Box 11)
    - 1977-78 (Box 11)
    - 1979 (Box 11)
    - 1972 (Box 12)
    - 1975 (Box 12)
    - 1975 (Box 12)
    - 1978-79 (Box 12)
    - 1978-79 (Box 12)
    - 1979 (Box 12)
    - 1986 (Box 12)
    - 1986 (Box 12)
    - 1986-87 (Box 12)
    - 1991-92 (Box 13)
    - 1990-91 (Box 13)
    - 1993-94 (Box 13)
    - 1992-93 (Box 13)
    - 1995-96 (Box 13)
    - 1979-80 (Box 13)
    - 1994-95 (Box 13)
    - 1987-88 (Box 13)
    - 1986-87 (Box 13)
    - 1986-87 (Box 14)
    - 1989-90 (Box 14)
    - 1988-89 (Box 14)
    - 1984-85 (Box 14)
    - 1982 (Box 14)
    - 1993-94 (Box 14)
    - 1982-83 (Box 14)
    - 1983-84 (Box 14)
  - Administrative and Educational records of Walter Harris, 1960s (Box 15)
  - Research files of Dolores Hayden, 1970s (Box 16)
  - Research files of Dolores Hayden, 1970s (Box 17)
  - Concept plan: Summitwood Village Center, 1978 August 1 (Box 18)
  - Yale Building project
    - 1995 (Box 19)
    - 1999 (Box 19)
    - 2000 (Box 19)
    - 2001 (Box 19)
    - 2002 (Box 19)
    - 2003 (Box 19)
    - 2004 (Box 19)
    - 2005 (Box 19)
    - 2006 (Box 19)
    - no date (Box 19)
    - photos, undated (Box 19)
    - Habitat for Humanity: Two Family House, 1990 (Box 20)
    - 50 Derby Avenue, 1997 April 28 (Box 21)
- Accreditation and building renovation reports, 1997-2003; Accession 2007-A-207
  Restricted until Jan 1,2039
  - National Architectural Accrediting Board (NAAB) Architectural Program Report, 1997
    - Volume 1, copy 1 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
    - Volume 2, copy 1 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
    - Volume 1, copy 2 (Box 1, Folder 9-13)
    - Volume 2, copy 2 (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
  - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill LLP, "Rudolph Building Renovation: Preliminary Design Report", 2003 July 1 (Box 2, Folder 17-21)
- Department of Architecture records, 1948-1953; Accession 2008-A-159
  Scope and Contents
  Gift of William S. Huff (M. Arch '52). See folder 2 for descriptions and recollections of Mr. Huff concerning documents in accession.
  The materials are open for research.
  - Original sketch in colored pencils by Gene Nalle, 1948-1949 (Box 1)
  - Brochure in two parts with faculty members and students; chair Harold Hauf on cover page (8 pp.), 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - "DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE, YALE UNIVERSITY, BASIC DESIGN COURSE," (6pp.), 1950 September (Box 1)
  - "DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE, YALE UNIVERSITY, DESIGN SCHEDULE (subject to change), FIRST SEMESTER" (3 pp.), 1950-1951 (Box 1)
  - DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE, YALE UNIVERSITY:Curriculum -- New Schedule, Adjusted to Old Schedule (7 pp.), 1950-1953 (Box 1)
  - "YALE UNIVERSITY-DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE, ADVANCED DESIGN II, SPRING TERM", 1950-1951 (Box 1)
  - Program for the 1951 Competition for the MAGNUS T. HOPPER MEMORIAL FELLOWSHIP in Hospital Architecture (Box 1)
  - Letter: "TO ALL STUDENTS IN THE DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE: George Howe Chairman" (Box 1)
  - "DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE, YALE UNIVERSITY: Talk Addressed to the (Assembled) Student Body of the Department, by George Howe, Chairman" (7 pp.), 1951 September 20 (Box 1)
  - "YALE UNIVERSITY-DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE; MEMORANDUM TO: ALL STUDENTS AND MEMBERS OF THE FACULTY, ARCHITECTURAL JURY PROCEDURES" (signed: George Howe Chairman) (2 pp.) (Box 1)
  - "ADV. DESIGN III, Prob. I, "A Concert Area in a Park in New Haven"; JURY: Cole, Coolidge, Kahn, Sawyer, Noyes, Wu, 1951 November 1 (Box 1)
  - "YALE UNIVERSITY, SCHOOL OF THE FINE ARTS, DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE: TEAM FOR COLLABORATIVE PROBLEM", 1951 November 14 (Box 1)
  - Ball graphic: "commedia dell' arte", 1952 May 2 (Box 1)
  - Student presentation: "SECTION II - ACOUSTICS"(5 pp.) (Box 1)
  - Letter: George Howe, to WHOM IT MAY CONCERN, 1952 June 17 (Box 1)
  - Letter: George Howe, to WHOM IT MAY CONCERN, 1952 June 17 (Box 1)
  - Multicolored study (gelatins mounted between plastic sheets) of one panel of the glass skin, designed by Jack Marmaras for the crocodiles and birds habitat building, circa 1951-1952 (Box 1A)
- Newsclippings and publications documenting the School of Architecture, 1963-2008; Accession 2009-A-020
  - Merchandising Interior Design, publication from symposium, 1989 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Art Gallery catalog, p 10 "The Architect's Table: Swid Powell and Postmodern Design", Fall 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yale China 100 with post-its marking faculty and students chosen to visit, 2007 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Architecture in Schools" ACSA publ., see pp 154-155, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "The Work of Paul Rudolph" check list of an exhibition at the Yale Art Gallery, 1963 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Log", Massimo Scolari, Winter spring 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - From the website of the Chronicle of Higher Education, "Art and Architecture Building Renovations Approach Completion at Yale U.", 2008 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Metropolis magazine, "Hawaii's Lost Master" and Hawaiian Modern poster, 2008 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The New Journal, Vol. 40 No.4 p.17, 2008 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "The Best Laid Plans" by Ali Seitz (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Architectural Forum 4 copies of Rudolph Building article, 1964 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alexander Garvin's 905b Int. Planning and Development course spring 2008, "Developing Kaufman Astoria" (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Course syllabi, 2009; Accession 2010-A-096; 0.25
  - 1011a Architectural Design – Ben Pell, Sunil Bald, Martin Cox, Joyce Hsiang, Jennifer Leung, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1015a Vizualization II: Form and Representation – Sunil Bald, Kent Bloomer, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1021a Architectural Design – Mark Gage, Martin finio, Joel Sanders, Peter de Bretteville, Makram el Kadi, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2021a Environmental Design – Michelle Addington, Naomi Darling, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 4021 Intro to Planning and Development – Alexander Garvin, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2031a Architectural Practice and Management – Phillip Bernstein, John Apicella, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1061a Post Pro Architectural Design – Edward Mitchell, Fred Koetter, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1062a Computation Analysis Fabrication – John Eberhart, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 3091a Methods and Research – Karla Britton, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 551a PhD Seminar I – Kurt Forster, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1224a The Chair – Timothy Newton, Joshua Rowley, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Syllabus/Chair as Crucible for Architectural Design, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2217 Material Formation in Design – Kevin Rotheroe (class cancelled), Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2220a Studies in Light and Materials – Michelle Addington, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2227a Design and Disease: New Typologies – Hilary Sample, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 3011a Modern Architecture and Society - Kurt Forster, Daniel Sherer, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 3021a Case Studies in Architectural Theory – Emmanuel Petit, Marta Caldeira, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 3217a Writing on Architecture – Carter Wiseman, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3218a Architectural Theories on Environment – Ariane Lourie Harrison, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3222a Venice – Daniel Sherer, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3223a Parallels of the Modern: The New Tradition – Robert A.M. Stern, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3227a Tropical Architecture – Dean Sakamoto, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 4212a American Cultural Landscape – Dolores Hayden, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 4221a Commercial Real Estate Principals and Practices – Kevin Gray, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 4222a History of Italian Landscape Architecture – Bryan Fuermann, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 4225a Learning from Landscape – Kathleen John-Alder, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1101a Advanced Studio – Lise Anne Couture w/ Brennan Buck, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1102a Advanced Studio – Leon Krier w/ George Knight, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1103a Advanced Studio – Gregg Pasquarelli w/Brian Price, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1104a Advanced Studio – Peter Eisenman w/ Michael Wang, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1105a Advanced Studio – Stefan Behnisch w/ John Eberhart, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1106a Advanced Studio - Mimi Hoang and Eric Bunge, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1107a Advanced Studio – China by Alan Plattus and Andrei Harwell, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 249a The Analytic Model – Emmanuel Petit, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arch 351/AMST 381 Poets' Landscape – Dolores Hayden, Fall 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Spring and Summer 2009
    - 512b Adv Studio – Greg Lynn w/ Brennan Buck (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 516b Adv Studio - John Patkau w/ Tim Newton (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 520b Adv Studio – William Sharples (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 520 b Adv Studio – William Sharples (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Seminar – Integrated Design and Construction – ShoP Architects (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Design and Visualization Study Area- John Eberhart, Hilary Sample (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Summer Visualization Studio 1001c –George Knight, Joyce Hsiang, Kyle Dugdale (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Arch 500c Summer Visualization Studio – History/theory component readings – Kyle Dugdale (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Records, 2001-2012; Accession 2013-A-002
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  The accession contains course evaluations, Spring 2012, A& A Building renovation correspondence, press kits, and faculty promotion and re-appointment materials, 2001-2012.
  - Arch 1012 Arch Design – Alan Organschi, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arch 1012 Arch Design- Jennifer Leung, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arch 1012 Arch Design – Peter de Bretteville, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arch 1012 Arch Design- Joeb Moore, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arch 1012 Arch Design-Joel Sanders, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arch 1016 Visualization III –Fabrication John Eberhart, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arch 1016 Visualization III –Fabrication Ben Pell, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arch 1022 Arch Design- Sunil Bald, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arch 1022 Arch Design- Peggy Deamer, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arch 1022 Arch Design- K. Easterling, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arch 1022 Arch Design- Alan Plattus, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arch 1022 Arch Design- Bimal Mendis, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arch 1022 Arch Design- Edw. Mitchell, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arch 1111 Adv. Studio – Greg Lynn, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arch 1111 Adv. Studio – Brennan Buck, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Arch 1112 Adv. Studio – Massimo Scolari, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arch 1112 Adv. Studio – Tim Newton, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arch 1113 Adv. Studio – Bjarke Ingels, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Arch 1113 Adv. Studio - Andrew Benner, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arch 1113Adv. Studio – Thomas Christofferson, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Arch 1113 Adv. Studio – Douglas Durst, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arch 1114 Adv. Studio- Frank Gehry, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Arch 1114 Adv. Studio- Trattie Davies, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Arch 1115 Adv. Studio- D. Porphyrios, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Arch 1115 Adv Studio – George Knight, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Arch 1115 Adv. Studio - Alejandro Zaera-Polo, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arch 1116 Adv. Studio - Ryan Welch, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Arch 1117 Adv. Studio- Joe Deegan-Day, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Arch 1117 Adv Studio – Michelle Paul, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Arch 1118 Adv. Studio- Deborah Berke, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Arch 1119 Adv. Studio- Noah Biklen, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arch 121 Books and Architecture – Luke Bulman, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Arch 1216 Ornament – Kent Bloomer, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Arch 1218 Furniture Design – Peter de Bretteville, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Arch 1218 Furniture Design – Brian Butterfield, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Arch 1222 Diagrammatic Analysis – Peter Eisenman, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Arch 1226 Site & Building – Steven Harris, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Arch 1227 Drawing Projects – Turner Brooks, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Arch 1228 Disheveled Geometries- Mark Gage, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Arch 1229 Display & Fabrication –B. Pell, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Arch 1231 Assembly – Brennan Buck, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Arch 2012 Structures II – K.S. Moon, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Arch 2015 Building Technology – Alan Organschi, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Arch 2015 Building Technology – Adam Hopfner, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – Lisa Davey, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – A. Bellomio, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration- M. Finio - Coordinator, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – N. Dando-Haenisch, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – E. Hatfield, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – R. Haughney, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration- K. Hawkins, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – J.Jacobson, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – A. Marchesin, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – Charles Brown, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – Pierce Reynoldson, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – Craig Razza, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – T. DiBlasi, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – Ed Stanley, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – Phil Steiner, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – Paul Stoller, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – A. Trojanowski, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Arch 2022 Systems Integration – L. Turlington, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Arch 2216 Materials & Meaning – Deborah Berke, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Arch 2219 Craft, Materials & Computer Aided Design - Kevin Rotheroe, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Arch 2221 –Ornament & Technology – Ben Pell N/A, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    General
    Folder not received from office.
  - Arch 2224 Issues in Contemporary Practice – Phil Bernstein, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Arch 2224 Issues in Contemporary Practice – John Apicella, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Arch 2226 Design Computation – Jason Van Nest, Spring 2012 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Arch 3022 Arch Theory II:1968-present Ariane Lourie Harrison, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 69-70)
  - Arch 3214 Construction of Exactitude – Karla Britton, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Arch 3216 Case Studies in Arch Criticism – Carter Wiseman, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Arch 3221Performance Criticism:Banham – K. Krumwiede, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Arch 3225 Religion & Modern Arch – Karla Britton, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Arch 3233 Venturi Scott Brown & Assoc – Stanislaus von Moos, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Arch 3227 Human/Nature – J. Sanders, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Arch 3239 Launch:Arch& Entrepreneurship – K. Easterling, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Arch 3243 Cold Ward Urbanism: Berlin – Stanislaus von Moos, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Arch 3246 From Open City to Post-Modern City – Marta Caldeira, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Arch 3248 Schinkel & the European City – Kurt Forster, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Arch 3249 Exhibit Architecture – Eeva-Liisa Pelkonen, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Arch 3250 Minimally Invasive Dialogues – Joe Deegan Day, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Arch 4011 Intro to Urban Design – Alan Plattus, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Arch 4011 Intro to Urban Design – Andrei Harwell, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Arch 4011 Intro to Urban Design – Elihu Rubin, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Arch 4211 Intermed. Planning & Dev. – Alexander Garvin, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Arch 4214 Built environ & Politics of – Dolores Hayden, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Arch 4219 Urban Research & Representation – Elihu Rubin, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Arch 4223 History of British Landscape- Bryan Fuermann, Spring 2012 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - A&A Building Renovation Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - A&A Building Renovation Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - A&A Building Renovation Correspondence, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - A&A Building Renovation Correspondence, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 93-95)
  - A&A Building Renovation Correspondence, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - A&A Rededication, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Jeanne Collins Associates Report on highlights of press coverage for Yale' new arts complex, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Press kits, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Faculty promotion and tenure materials
    Restricted until January 1, 2086.
    - Re-Appointment materials for Hilary Sample, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Re-Appointment materials for K.S. Moon, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Re-Appointment materials for Thomas Beeby, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Re-Appointment materials for Deborah Berke, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Re-Appointment materials for John Jacobson, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Re-Appointment materials for Edward Mitchell, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Dean's Council including Berlin Trip, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Dean's file on Admissions Watch List, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Records, 1983-2009; Accession 2013-A-024
  Restricted until January 1, 2047.
  The accession consists of architecture student rules forms and course evaluations.
  - Architecture students rules forms-old forms, 1983-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1-8)
    Includes records on the 1997 YSOA student elections.
  - Architecture students rules forms-old forms, 2002-2009 (Box 2, Folder 9-43)
  - Architecture course evaluations, 2008 Spr (Box 3, Folder 44-104)
- Records, 1996-2013; Accession 2014-A-049
  - Alumni correspondence
    The alumni correspondence is restricted until January 1, 2047, as established by actuate="onRequest" show="new" href="http://web.library.yale.edu/mssa/collections/research-use-of-yale-university-archives" Yale Corporation.
    - 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 2010-2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Course syllabi
    - 161b Intro to Structures, 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 491b/494b Senior Project Tutorial-Karla Britton, 2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 501a Architectural Design-course readings, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 502b Architectural Design, 2000 Spring-2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 503a Architectural Design, 1999 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 504b Architectural Design, 2001 Fall-2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 504b Architectural Design/Building Project, 2001, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8A)
    - 507b Digital Workshop, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 509a/523a Post Pro Studio, 2004 Fall-2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 511a-524b Advanced Studios, 1999-2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 601a Structures, 1999 Fall-2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 602b Structures II, 2000 Spring-2006 Spring (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 614b Structures and Architecture-Polemics and Practice, 1996 Spring-1997 Spring (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 625a The Liquid Threshold Between Order and Chaos, 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 633a Environmental Design, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)